Welcome back.
In the section, we are going to see how to develop a USP device.
Or we going to see how to develop USP devices using a Y ASTM 32 microcontroller in the same experiment,
which will be using in the Discovery Board because the Discovery Port has this extra USP port over here
that would allow us to use a white board as a device.
So basically, if we can't figure out the board as a mouse, we would have to connect a USP here and
then connect it to our computer so that we can be moving the disco board as if it were a mouse.
The new clue hasn't got this, but the code you learn here would work exactly on any board.
Remember, the microcontroller chip is where we are programming.
The reason why the new clue cannot be used in this experiment is just because the new clue hasn't got
this metallic fin here to allow us to connect or USP.
But internally, if we flush the cord onto the new two DSP pins, which are normal GPL Europeans don't
become forget to save us USP Moonen.
If you buy your own SDM Pettitte two for one one microcontroller this chip and you flush the quote out,
we are going to write if you flush it and then you sold everything including a USB port to it.
And what I mean by USB port is just this metallic thing.
If you saw it out, it should be able to work.
But for our experiments sake, we already have a disco ball to house all of this sorted.
So we'll be using this, right.
So in the next lesson, we should go ahead and configure our USP.
Our disco board to work as if it's where it mounts.
We're going to see how to create a USP HIIT device.
HIV stands for human interface device.
And this human interface device is going to be a mouse.
So see you the next lesson.